[Music]
welcome to another episode of what's
cooking today we'll show you another
Nifty little addition to Business Center
2025 wave 1 developed by one of our
community members let me show you how
you can limit the amount of available
product
languages as we all know if you go into
my settings and you pick language
there's a large list to choose from
which can be rather confusing to the end
user
us going forward administrators have the
ability to go into allowed
languages we can specify Which languages
you would like the user to be able to
choose from so let's say we select the
danishes in a loud
language and
English there we
go now if you go into my
settings the user will only be able to
choose from the languages which are
allowed for information there's a little
uh notification showing here that this
is now a filtered
view as I mentioned uh this was a
partner contribution Casper suggested uh
this feature and also suggested that it
can develop it and even though it didn't
get a whole lot of votes uh our product
manager said this is fine this would be
a great
addition so Casper went ahead and uh
went on to to GitHub and created this
pull request that enables his capability
which then now ships with 2025 wave 1
thanks for watching